What's going on here?
But most of all, I'm...
Okay, settle down.
I'm...
Take it easy.
What the scallop?!
I'm a Goofy Goober
CHORUS:  Rock
Ahhh!
You're a Goofy Goober
Rock!
We're all Goofy Goobers
Goofy-goofy-goober-goober
Rock!
Put your toys away
Well, all I gotta say
When you tell me not to play
I say no way
No way!
No, no freaking way
( all laughing )
I'm a kid, you say
When you say I'm a kid
I say, "Say it again"
And then I say thanks
Thanks!
Thank you very much
So if you're thinking
That you'd like to be like me
Go ahead and try
The kid inside
Will set you free
Hama-la, baby-la
Zeebilay, boobilay
Zeebilay, bop
I'm a Goofy Goober
Rock!
PLANKTON:
Ohhh...
What's happening?
Huh?
His dance moves are impressive.
But I'm in control!
Seize him!
ALL ( droning ):
All hail Plankton.
Yeahhhhh!
( playing wild solo )
Whoo!
I'm free. I've been freed!
What?
No!
- Yay!
- Ah!
( all cheer )
My precious helmets!
- Ha!
- Hoo!
Yee-haw!
Meow.
ALL ( droning ):
Yay.
( all whooping, cheering )
PLANKTON:
His chops are too righteous.
The helmets can't handle
this level of rock 'n' roll.
Karen, do something.
Karen?
Agh!
All right,
that's the last straw.
Neptune, I command you to...
Here you go, Daddy.
I...better get outta here.
Look, it's the wizard
who saved us.
Out of my way, fools.
Ow!
Aghhhh!
Come on, I was just kidding.
So, yeah, I'm a kid.
And I'm also a goofball.
And a wing nut.
And a Knucklehead McSpazatron!
What?
( coughing )